

# Mario González Duarte

FRONT END DEVELOPER

#### **Profile**

Professional with 15+ years of experience in web development with a wide range of technical skills and a deep understanding of the latest technologies and trends in front end development. Ability to be decisive. Committed, dedicated, proactive and collaborative, with a predisposition both for teamwork and for helping and/or transmitting knowledge, providing mentoring and support. Always learning. In addition to development, I'm also interested in technical lead and front end architect roles.

# **Work Experience**

## **Freelance**

Madrid (Spain)

July 2022 - Present

Working on various projects related to web3 and blockchain technology.

- Design and development of a marketplace for Stream Dungeons NFT game, in Angular and SASS (https://nft.streamdungeons.com)
- Collaboration in the creation from scratch of a play-to-earn game, with React and SASS.
- Creation of a new online resume, in React and SASS.
- Update my expertise and skills in both Angular and React, taking training courses.

# Front end developer and Architect, Copado Holdings Inc

Madrid (Spain)

May 2019 - July 2022

I worked on some of the best known applications of the company such as Data Templates, Pipeline and creating Value Stream Maps from scratch.

- Designed and developed generic Lightning Web Components to be reused by other developers in other parts of the application.
- Worked closely with the design department to convert the new company look and feel design in real CSS layouts.
- Refactoring and technical support to workmates.

#### Front end Architect, VASS

Madrid (Spain)

November 2017 - May 2019

Hired as a front end architect to collaborate in the design and development of different company projects Angular applications, several onboardings apps and various POC projects.

- Designed and developed an Angular library made up of components to be used by developers in their projects.
- Implemented a front end architecture in Ferrovial.
- Technical support to workmates and technical interviews to new candidates.

#### Javascript front end developer, Efron Consulting Inc

Boston, MA. USA

April 2015 - November 2017

- I worked at Isban developing different internal Santander USA bank applications.
- I designed and built a development environment which provided an architecture and a controlled environment to programming, in order to give crossover components and widgets to be used by developers in their projects.

#### **Details**

Madrid, Spain

magodu.pral@gmail.com

**L** +34 679 84 97 84

September 26th 1982

www.mariogonzalezduarte.es

#### Skills

Angular

React

Javascript

Typescript

Lightning Web Components

AngularJS

jQuery

Webpack

HTML5

CSS / SASS / LESS

Responsive Design

**API REST** 

Git

Node JS

Jest

TDD

Agile Methodologies

Adobe Photoshop

# Languages





Spanish

**Enalish** 

### Javascript front end developer, Adesis Netlife SL

Madrid, Spain October 2011 - April 2015

• Javascript developer in important customers such as BBVA Bancomer Mexico, Repsol, Bankia and Mapfre.

- At Mapfre, I worked in the establishment of a new and better front end architecture, developing new crossover component, initial developments (Zero versions) and experimental projects.
- Managed an small development group at Bankia.

### Front end developer, Atmira Espacio de consultoría

Madrid, Spain November 2008 - October 2015

I worked in Web applications for several Saving Banks at Confederación Española de Cajas de Ahorros (CECA).

### Scholarship assistant, Cantabria Government Admin.

Santander, Spain August 2006 - October 2008

Scholarship assistant at Cantabria Education office (Spain), doing admin tasks as webmaster in the government educative site (Educantabria)

#### **Education**

Higher Level Training Cycle (CFGS) in Management Information Systems. Computer and Information Sciences.

IES Alisal. Santander, Spain

# Other interesting data

Drive license B

Hobbies: photography, films and TV shows, music, traveling,

dancing, technology, reading

**Linkedin:** https://www.linkedin.com/in/mario-gonzalez-duarte

**Github:** https://github.com/magodu **More info:** www.mariogonzalezduarte.es

#### Courses

React Angular

Typescript LWC

Clean Code AngularJS

NodeJS Memory Leaks

Closures Polymer

.NET Web design

Photoshop E-commerce

Java